The next step in doing a hand massage is for you and your client to sanitize your hands.
You want to use an improved hand sanitizer or you want to use soap and warm water.
Make sure that you rub the fronts real good, the backs of the hands also go ahead and rub the wrists.
Make sure that it's nice and clean.
If you need a little extra hand sanitizer go ahead and put some in.
If you're using your sink you always want to make sure you wash your hands for at least a full thirty seconds to a minute.
Once you're hand sanitizer dries up you know you've used it all.
Again, this one is Germ-X.
It's what we're using today, but if you have access to soap and water it's best to go ahead and use that.
You want to make sure that if you have an open wound or if your client has a cut on her hand already that she's not going to get infection in it.
The best way to do that is by keeping your hands clean.
That is how you sanitize your hands.